[Music]
it's been said that it's natural to have
mixed emotions
from being over the moon to over
worrying
motherhood is an amazing journey
offering priceless experience
from the minute you find out that you
are pregnant
and you watch your baby bump grow each
day it seems like time goes so fast yet
so slow all at the same time
you breathe a little differently now
you watch your body transform and see a
different reflection in the mirror now
trying to still be yourself
while picturing being a mother
the weight is both thrilling and
terrifying
all those choppy sleeps backaches
morning sickness leg cramps and checkups
and you count down the weeks
you want to make sure to give the best
to your little one
researching to get the best baby
products while taking off everything in
your checklist
it is a precious gift
one that matters most to you
which is why you choose the best
assurance there is
manual life precious gift provides early
protection that begins in the womb for a
mother to be and your precious little
one
giving you complete peace of mind during
those delicate months of pregnancy from
as early as 13 weeks into pregnancy
protection against the unexpected
hospitalization benefits
emotional health support and more to
support you and your little one through
this crucial period in life
you can also secure a comprehensive
medical coverage for your pre-born child
for life that is beautiful and filled
with blessing choose manual life
precious gift to walk the journey with
you
cherish and treasure every precious
moment
find out more by visiting our website
calling our customer caroline or get in
touch with your manual life advisor
today